( WIND BLOWING )
- ( FOOTSTEPS THUMPING ) - ( HEAVY BREATHING )
( HORSE WHINNIES )
( HORSES WHINNYING )
( WIND WHISTLING )
( DOOR OPENS )
( FOOTSTEPS THUMP )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( BLEATING )
( HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( WOMAN SPEAKING ON RADIO IN ICELANDIC )
( SHEEP BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO )
( WIND WHISTLING )
( CHRISTMAS SONG PLAYING ON RADIO )
( DRINK POURING )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY ON RADIO )
( INCREASES VOLUME )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO )
( CAT MEOWS )
( MARIA GRUNTS )
- ( LAMB BLEATS ) - ( SIGHS )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
MARIA : Mmm .
( INGVAR CHUCKLES )
( CLEARS THROAT )
( BLEATS )
( MARIA SHUSHING )
( WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY )
( RECORD PLAYER SKIPPING )
( BREATHES DEEPLY )
( WATER POURING )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( THUDS )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING )
( CAT MEOWS )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( LAMB BLEATS )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( DOG BARKING )
( DOG WHINING )
( BLEATS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( MARIA GASPS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( LAMB BLEATING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( BLEATS )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( INGVAR SIGHS DEEPLY )
( SIGHS )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( RADIO PLAYING INDISTINCTLY )
( MARIA HUMMING )
( HUMMING CONTINUES )
( STOPS HUMMING )
( CONTINUES HUMMING )
( SIGHS )
( ENGINE IDLING )
( SNIFFLES )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
( SIGHS )
( SOBS QUIETLY )
( SIGHS DEEPLY )
( ENGINE REVS )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( SHEEP BREATHING HEAVILY )
( ENGINE STOPS )
( GRUNTS )
( BARKS )
( DOG WHINES )
( DOG PANTING , WHINING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS )
( TRACTOR ENGINE STARTS )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
- ( LAMB BLEATS IN DISTANCE ) - ( SHEEP BLEATS )
( MARIA SHOOING SHEEP )
( BLEATS )
( INGVAR SHOOS )
- ( SHEEP BLEATS ) - ( LAMB BLEATS )
( MARIA AND INGVAR SHOOING )
( TV PLAYING )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( LAMB BLEATS )
( TV CONTINUES PLAYING )
( SHEEP BLEATING IN DISTANCE )
( BLEATS )
( BLOWS )
( MACHINE WHIRRING )
( SHEEP BLEATING IN DISTANCE )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY )
( DOG BARKS )
( DOG BARKING )
( PANTING )
- ( MARIA PANTING ) - ( LAMB BLEATS IN DISTANCE )
( GASPS )
( BOTH PANTING )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( SHOUTING )
( DOG BARKS )
( INGVAR SIGHS )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( BLEATING )
( INGVAR URGING SHEEP )
( CONTINUES URGING )
( RINGTONE PLAYING ON CELL PHONE )
( RINGTONE STOPS PLAYING )
- ( CELL PHONE CLATTERS ) - ( MAN GROANS )
( ENGINE STARTS )
( UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON CAR STEREO )
( MAN SHOUTS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( LABORED BREATHING )
( BLEATING )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( RAIN PATTERING )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( BLEATING CONTINUES )
( DOG WHINING )
( SHEEP BLEATS )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PAYING )
( BLEATING CONTINUES )
- ( GUNSHOT ) - ( SHEEP THUDS )
( PANTING )
- ( WATER RUNNING ) - ( SCRUBBING )
( ENGINE STARTING )
( GRUNTS SOFTLY )
( SIGHS )
( TRACTOR IDLING IN DISTANCE )
- ( INGVAR SPEAKING ) - ( MAN SPEAKING )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( SIGHS )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( CHAIR DRAGS )
( LAUGHS )
Oh . ( LAUGHING )
( COOING )
( MARIA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY )
( MARIA CHUCKLES )
( LAUGHING )
( WHISPERS )
( SIGHS )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( WHINING )
( DOG BARKS )
( DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE )
( DOG WHINING )
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
( SIGHS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( PETUR GRUNTS )
- ( INGVAR SPEAKING ) - ( PETUR SPEAKING )
( CHUCKLES )
( DRUM BEATING )
( ADA FUSSES )
( SIGHS )
( SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING )
( ADA PANTING )
( GASPS SOFTLY )
( SIGHS )
( PANTING )
( ENGINE STARTS )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( MOANS SOFTLY )
( GASPS )
( ENGINE STOPS )
( ENGINE STALLING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
Mmm-hmm .
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( PETUR GRUNTS TIREDLY )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( POURING )
( TV PLAYING )
( BOTH EXCLAIM SOFTLY )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( MAN COMMENTATING ON TV )
( COMMENTARY ON TV CONTINUES )
( DOG WHINING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( MUSIC PLAYING ON TV )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
Mmm-mmm .
( MARIA LAUGHING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
- ( DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES ON TV ) - ( PETUR MOUTHING ALONG )
( MARIA LAUGHING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES )
( PETUR WHOOPS , LAUGHS )
( LAUGHING )
( MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING FAINTLY )
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
( BARKING )
( DOG WHIMPERS )
( GROANS )
- Oh ! - ( PETUR AND MARIA LAUGH )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( MARIA SPEAKING )
( GROANS )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( GRUNTS )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
( OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING )
( DOG BARKING )
( PETUR SIGHS , SPEAKING )
( CHUCKLES )
( LAUGHS )
( PETUR SIGHS )
( MARIA BREATHING HEAVILY )
( PETUR GROANS )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
( KNOCKS ON DOOR )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( PIANO PLAYING )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
- ( DOORKNOB RATTLING ) - ( PIANO CONTINUES PLAYING )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
( STOPS PLAYING )
( SOFT FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
Hmm ?
( EXHALES )
( WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO )
- ( RADIO CONTINUES PLAYING ) - ( INGVAR SPEAKING )
( INGVAR SIGHS )
( SIGHS )
( TURNS OFF RADIO )
( CAT MEOWS )
( WHISTLES )
( PETUR CLEARS THROAT )
( PETUR SPEAKING )
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
( UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO )
( ENGINE STALLING )
( CONTINUES STALLING )
( SIGHS IN EXASPERATION )
Hmm .
( MARIA SPEAKING )
- ( GUNSHOT IN DISTANCE ) - ( GASPS )
( PANTING )
( GROANING )
- ( GUNSHOT ) - ( GROANS )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
- ( FOOTSTEPS THUMPING ) - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( PANTING )
( BREATHING WEAKLY )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY )
( ADA WHIMPERING )
( GRUNTING )
- ( GASPING ) - ( FOOTSTEPS RECEDING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPING )
( CRYING )
( CONTINUES CRYING )
( SOBBING )
( BREATHING SHAKILY )
( SNIFFLES )
( BREATHES SHAKILY )
( INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING )